lotterycanada.com 2006-06-15

# Privacy Statement on Lottery Canada

<[more info](http://www.lotterycanada.com/lottery/?job=site_news#RSS)>  

Privacy Statement

Lottery Canada has created this privacy policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information.

Our site contains:

  * registration forms that requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. 
  * order forms for customers to request information. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address). The customer's contact information is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. 
  * online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their email address). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary.
  * contests in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. 
  * links to other sites. Lottery Canada is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can send email to [info@lotterycanada.com](mailto:info@lotterycanada.com)
  2. You can visit the following URL: [http://www.lotterycanada.com](http://www.lotterycanada.com/)

Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. email [info@lotterycanada.com](mailto:info@lotterycanada.com)
  2. visit [http://www.lotterycanada.com](http://www.lotterycanada.com/)

Contact Information

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with our Web site, you can contact 

Lottery Canada Email: [privacy@lotterycanada.com](mailto:privacy@lotterycanada.com) |  | 

All lottery results are unofficial. Please check with your local lottery retailer for confirmation.  
Application & Design by Q9 Media. Copyright © 2000-2006 LotteryCanada.com. All rights reserved.  
Read our [Privacy Statement](http://www.lotterycanada.com/lottery/?job=privacy_statement) or [Disclaimer](http://www.lotterycanada.com/lottery/?job=disclaimer).
